const questions = [
  {
    question: "Which company became the first to reach a $2 trillion market cap in 2020?",
    options: ["Google", "Apple", "Microsoft", "Amazon"],
    answer: "Apple",
  },
  {
    question: "Which African country launched its first satellite into space?",
    options: ["Nigeria", "Egypt", "Ghana", "South Africa"],
    answer: "Ghana",
  },
  {
    question: "When did Twitter announce the 'Super Follows' feature?",
    options: ["2020", "2021", "2019", "2022"],
    answer: "2021",
  },
  {
    question: "Which mobile payment service, launched in Kenya, has expanded across Africa?",
    options: ["Paystack", "Flutterwave", "M-Pesa", "Airtel Money"],
    answer: "M-Pesa",
  },
  {
    question: "Which company's CEO announced plans to build a city called 'Starbase' in Texas?",
    options: ["Amazon", "SpaceX", "Tesla", "Blue Origin"],
    answer: "SpaceX",
  },
  {
    question: "What service specializes the Nigerian tech startup Flutterwave in?",
    options: ["Social media", "E-commerce", "Payment processing", "Online education"],
    answer: "Payment processing",
  },
  {
    question: "Which technology is primarily associated with cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin?",
    options: ["Artificial Intelligence", "Quantum Computing", "Blockchain", "Virtual Reality"],
    answer: "Blockchain",
  },
  {
    question: "As of 2021, which country is leading Africa in tech start-up investments?",
    options: ["South Africa", "Nigeria", "Kenya", "Egypt"],
    answer: "Nigeria",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the major new feature in Apple's iPhone 12, released in 2020?",
    options: ["Foldable screen", "5G capability", "Solar charging", "3D camera"],
    answer: "5G capability",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main purpose of Rwanda's drone delivery service, launched in 2016?",
    options: ["Package delivery", "Medical supply delivery", "Surveillance", "Agricultural monitoring"],
    answer: "Medical supply delivery",
  }
];
